(Howard:)Yeah, I've worked with Hawking,
I talked you up. He knows your research.
(Howard:)- I think this could happen.
- He kno...?
(Leonard:)Wow.
Wait, now, but do you think
that's a good idea?
(Sheldon:)You know Star Trek.
(Sheldon:)Should a guy with no name
and a red shirt really go on an expedition?
(Raj:)Hey, don't discourage him.
This is a fantastic opportunity.
(Sheldon:)No one asked you, Uhura.
(Sheldon:)Would you like to hear a classic
Sheldon Cooper factoid?
- What do you think?
- Great.
(Sheldon:)I've been doing some reading
about vehicular safety.
(Sheldon:)Did you know that the highest number
of drowning accidents...
(Sheldon:)...happen on or around boats?
(Leonard:)Interesting that you would bring that up
when I might go work on a boat.
(Sheldon:)Well, that's the thing about factoids,
they're interesting.
(Leonard:)I know what you're doing.
You don't want me going on this trip
because you're afraid to be alone.